Can I ask for help?
我可以请求帮忙吗？
Don't disturb him.
别打扰他。
You still love him.
你还爱他。
He always wants to help me.
他总是想帮助我。
but we
但我们
A man from two worlds.
是一个来自两个世界的人。
They are destined not to be together forever.
注定不会永远在一起。
what about me
关于我的什么
I...
我...
you...
你...
Are we
我们是吗
People from the same world?
来自同一个世界的人？
it depends on whether you can help me
这取决于你能否帮助我
achieve my goals.
实现我的目标。
it feels right
感觉是对的
You are always very rational.
你总是很理性。
Life is already very difficult
生活已经很困难了
too emotional
太情绪化
The game could end at any time.
游戏随时可能结束。
game
游戏
at first i
起初我
due to proxy games
由于代理游戏
[Because of the agency game. 】
【因为代理游戏。】
So everything that happens after this
所以这之后发生的一切
It can only be regarded as a game
只能算是一个游戏
continue
继续
Due to the mission of the agent
由于代理人的使命
Because the agent’s mission
因为代理人的使命
sorry.
对不起。
Why are you apologizing to me?
你为什么要向我道歉？
this game
这个游戏
I know
我知道
if it's because of him
如果是因为他
Let you become like this,
让你变成这样，
Because he hurt you.
因为他伤害了你。
I apologize to you on his behalf.
我代表他向你道歉。
Your friend?
你的朋友？
I'm with him
我和他在一起
for a long time
许久
in the agent's mission
在代理人的使命中
The code is
代码是
Z。
Z。
While studying at university,
在大学学习期间，
Developed with some friends
是和一些朋友一起开发的
A question and answer website.
一个问答网站。
Z is also one of them.
Z也是其中之一。
Everyone has the same ambition.
每个人都有同样的抱负。
Have lofty ambitions
有远大的志向
Want to be an academically rigorous person
想做一个学术严谨的人
[Q&A website]
[问答网站]
Q&A website.
问答网站。
But after the website went online,
但网站上线后，
Operating conditions are very harsh.
经营条件非常恶劣。
There are not many users.
用户不多。
our money
我们的钱
has been placed
已放入
Z goes to even numbered places.
Z 去偶数的地方。
Looking for investors,
寻找投资者，
But the collision is fun.
但碰撞很有趣。
The website has no follow-up investment
网站无后续投资
and ran into problems.
并遇到问题。
So we all went out.
于是我们都出去了。
Only Z survived.
只有Z幸存。
But even now,
但即使是现在，
Z is still unwilling to give up.
Z仍不甘心放弃。
at this time,
此时，
he saw
他看见
Announcement on the school website.
学校网站上的公告。
The school is holding
学校正在举办
Game design competition.
游戏设计比赛。
winner
优胜者
There is a $50,000 reward.
有50,000美元的奖励。
Seeing this news,
看到这个消息，
Z was like finding a life-saving straw.
Z就像找到了一根救命稻草。
Because we are several people
因为我们是几个人
Like to play games.
喜欢玩游戏。
I had no homework in school before
以前在学校没有作业
he did
他做了
some mini games
一些小游戏
Z Select one of the games.
Z 选择其中一场比赛。
While making games
制作游戏的同时
we are new here
我们是新来的
After watching spy
看完间谍后
It feels very stylish.
感觉非常时尚。
Z will take a few days.
Z需要几天时间。
Not day and night
不是白天和黑夜
Fixed reprogramming.
修复了重新程序。
Take this to the competition.
拿着这个参加比赛。
Mr. Zhou.
周先生。
Hello.
你好。
Are you OK
你好吗
I really admire
我真的很佩服
this is your game
这是你的游戏
Sadly
可悲的是
The judge didn't like that.
法官不喜欢这样。
have you ever thought about
你有没有想过
grow the game
发展这个游戏
Let everyone be in their corner of the world
让每个人在世界的角落
Play games like you
像你一样玩游戏
honestly,
诚实地，
i need more
我需要更多
$50,000.
50,000 美元。
I can give you $500,000.
我可以给你50万美元。
What conditions?
什么条件？
Keep evolving your game.
不断发展你的游戏。
As per my request.
按照我的要求。
but i don't want to
但我不想
Develop the game again
再次开发游戏
If so, let me ask you.
如果是的话，让我问你。
Why do you need so much money?
你为什么需要这么多钱？
Because I have a website.
因为我有一个网站。
i need this money
我需要这笔钱
to maintain operations.
以维持运营。
That's it.
就是这样。
In addition to these costs,
除了这些费用之外，
I will pay you
我会付你钱的
All research expenses.
所有研究费用。
If the research is successful
如果研究成功的话
I still have a bonus.
我还有奖金。
you can use it
你可以使用它
Do whatever you like.
做任何你喜欢的事。
In order to obtain this investment,
为了获得这笔投资，
to obtain that investment.
以获得该投资。
Find weaknesses and fill needs.
找到弱点并满足需求。
That's it
就是这样
This is commonly used by Mr. Yu.
这是于先生常用的。
He provides Z with a set of
他向Z提供了一组
Tell Z to follow his request
告诉 Z 遵循他的要求
Reschedule game
重新安排游戏
will become
会变成
Agent tasks now
现在代理任务
Then?
然后？
is it her
是她吗
Visit the site again
再次访问该网站
of.
的。
then he
然后他
Friends who have worked together before
以前一起工作过的朋友
All have been found.
都已经找到了。
and invest all the money
并投资所有的钱
pity
可惜
Not promoted properly.
没有适当推广。
Add US market
添加美国市场
At that time, this question and answer website
当时这个问答网站
Quite full.
相当满。
No one has asked about our website
我们的网站没有人问过
Capital investment
资金投入
All will be in vain.
一切都将是徒劳的。
why are you so
为什么你这么
Start reading philosophy yourself?
自己开始阅读哲学吗？
I guessed then
那时我猜想
Continue to do so in the United States,
在美国继续这样做，
There is certainly no future in sight.
肯定看不到未来。
But in China, the situation is different.
但在中国，情况不同。
It wasn't available at that time.
那个时候还没有。
Products of the same type appear.
出现相同类型的产品。
I want to return to China and start a business.
我要回国创业。
Make a philosophy book.
制作一本哲学书。
philosophy
哲学
It's a relationship
是关系
With an agent's mission
带着代理人的使命
Who are you
你是
like
喜欢
Very interesting to know
很有趣知道
maybe it's because of me
也许是因为我
in the agent's mission
在代理人的使命中
so
所以
for these questions.
对于这些问题。
But the story cannot be discussed all at once.
但故事不能一下子讨论完。
last question.
最后一个问题。
So this Z
那么这个Z
What about him?
那么他呢？
Mana Z?
法力Z？
Then there was a new plan
之后就有了新的计划
Agency mission
代理使命
just a beginning
只是一个开始
It has passed
已经过去了
The story ends here.
这个故事到这里就结束了。
I sent you back.
我把你送回来了。
Do not lie to me.
不要骗我。
Drink again.
再喝一次。
Pour again.
再倒一次。
again.
再一次。
will you help me
你会帮我吗
of.
的。
how can I help you?
我怎么帮你？
I need to investigate
我需要调查
Zhu Zheri’s true identity.
朱哲日的真实身份。
this matter
这件事
for me.
为我。
He betrayed you.
他背叛了你。
You don't have to worry about him.
你不用担心他。
of.
的。
Wasn't he threatened?
他没有受到威胁吗？
That wasn't his intention.
那不是他的本意。
You don't have to release him.
你不必释放他。
No matter what the reason is,
不管是什么原因，
Regardless of whether he was forced to
不管他是被迫的，
He is a spy.
他是一名间谍。
You lied to me again.
你又骗我了。
how is it like?
什么样的？
I think he believes me.
我想他相信我。
Zhu Zhe's daily dream
朱哲日梦望
terhadap Shi Qi.
terhadap Shi Qi.
How is he now?
他现在怎么样了？
He was saved.
他得救了。
Only minor injuries.
只有轻伤。
But then,
但接下来，
You will face big problems.
你将面临大问题。
Zhu Zhe must be suspicious of you.
朱哲一定是怀疑你了。
And reveal that.
并揭示这一点。
even doubt
甚至怀疑
You have a relationship with Guo An.
你和郭安有关系。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I won't admit it.
我不会承认。
not enough.
不够。
Make him trust you.
让他信任你。
is our goal.
是我们的目标。
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
To dispel his suspicion
为了打消他的怀疑
But there must be someone
但一定有一个人
Block the knife for you.
给你挡刀。
WHO？
WHO？
Huang Zicheng.
Huang Zicheng.
Did he ever tell you,
他有没有告诉过你，
Does he think there is something wrong with Zhu Zheri?
他认为朱哲日有问题吗？
You go find him.
你去找他吧。
Tell him you noticed.
告诉他你注意到了。
Ask him to help you investigate Zhu Zheri.
请他帮助你调查朱哲日。
He will definitely help you.
他一定会帮助你的。
It needs to be investigated whether it is true
是否属实要调查
of.
的。
You have to have a plan.
你必须有一个计划。
Then tell Zhu Zheri
然后告诉朱哲日
kepada Joo Cheol-il。
kepada Joo Cheol-il。
reject
拒绝
give him.
给他。
He is your surrender.
他就是你的投降书。
but...
但...
Is this necessary?
有必要这样做吗？
This is the best way now.
这是现在最好的办法了。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
He will survive.
他会活下去。
But if Huang Zicheng
但如果黄子成
Know that I betrayed him
知道我背叛了他
He will despair of you.
他会对你绝望。
and will never trust you again
并且永远不会再相信你
OK
好的。
I know.
我知道。
This is his recording.
这是他的录音。
philosophy.
哲学。
It's a relationship
是关系
With an agent's mission
带着代理人的使命
you
你
curiosity
好奇心
Very interesting to know
很有趣知道
maybe because i am
也许因为我是
Agent task player
代理任务玩家
so
所以
for these questions.
对于这些问题。
But the story cannot be discussed all at once.
但故事不能一下子讨论完。
last question.
最后一个问题。
So this Z
那么这个Z
What about him?
那么他呢？
Mana Z?
法力Z？
Then there was a new plan
之后就有了新的计划
Agency mission
代理使命
this is just the beginning
这只是一个开始
from start to finish,
从开始到结束，
He doesn't admit it
他不承认
He is the man of the night mist.
他是夜雾之人。
He doesn't admit it either
他也不承认
The relationship between the book of philosophy and the mission of the agent
哲学之书与特工使命的关系
He's not that easy
他没那么容易
so easy
这么容易
But he no longer doubts you.
但他不再怀疑你了。
that's right.
这是正确的。
Next?
下一个？
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
If Mr. Z is Zhu Zheri
如果Z先生是朱哲日的话
Then he is
那么他就是
Control agent game
控制代理游戏
you have to find a way
你必须找到一种方法
tear off his disguise
撕掉他的伪装
Look for evidence.
寻找证据。
of.
的。
I'll tell you what to do.
我会告诉你该怎么做。
OK
好的
At Zicheng's place
在子成那里
He's fine.
他没事。
He'll be out soon.
他很快就会出来。
He will hate me.
他会恨我的。
Hatred and misunderstanding are only temporary.
仇恨和误解只是暂时的。
everything you do now
你现在所做的一切
It's for the future.
是为了未来。
I'm not as good as you think.
我没有你想的那么好。
We now have two options.
我们现在有两个选择。
first
第一的
cooperate with me
与我合作
and killed him quietly.
并悄悄地杀了他。
What other options are there?
还有什么其他选择？
You can't kill him.
你不能杀他。
He has now surrendered to the National Security Bureau.
现已向国家安全局投案自首。
But he will be imprisoned.
但他会被监禁。
you come back.
你回来。
go to sleep.
去睡觉。
We will start taking action tomorrow.
我们将从明天开始行动。
I want to surrender.
我想投降。
are you sure?
你确定吗？
I'm sure.
我敢肯定。
Me and Bajiri
我和八吉里
i already told you
我已经告诉你
I told you
我告诉你了
Try telling me about your sister.
试着告诉我关于你妹妹的事。
tentang Yao Yue.
tentang Yao Yue.
my sisters
我的姐妹
Under their supervision,
在他们的监督下，
I can not
我不能
Took my sister's life.
夺走了我妹妹的生命。
so it's me
所以是我
Pretending to agree to Mr. Yu
假装答应于先生
to complete this task.
来完成这个任务。
He also promised me
他还答应我
After completing this task,
完成这个任务后，
will free my sister
会释放我妹妹
why are you so
为什么你这么
give up?
放弃？
because...
因为...
I can't kill anyone.
我不能杀人。
even if you think so
即使你这么认为
I'm a spy,
我是一名间谍，
but i'm still there
但我还在那里
I still have
我还有
You saved Huang Zicheng
你救了黄子成
This is also an opportunity
这也是一个机会
to make amends.
来弥补。
I see.
我明白。
Now task
现在任务
It’s to make Yagiri believe it
是为了让矢切相信
You and Tian Yang
你和田阳
out on a limb
无路可退
I can only kill Xiao Yi.
我只能杀了萧毅。
If that were the case, I'd still want to kill someone.
如果是这样，我还想杀人。
Do you trust us?
你信任我们吗？
I believe.
我相信。
we won't let you
我们不会让你
Do something illegal.
做违法的事情。
to help you make amends.
来帮助你弥补。
knew?
知道了？
understand.
理解。
from now on
今后
You are connected to the single sun
你与单一的太阳相连
Must obey his instructions
必须服从他的指示
Don't reveal your relationship.
不要透露你们的关系。
Your task information
您的任务信息
to anyone
对任何人
able
能
I can.
我可以。
what to do next
接下来做什么
The sun will tell you
太阳会告诉你
Don't look anymore
不要再看
I don't want to cook today.
我今天不想做饭。
Is this beautiful?
这漂亮吗？
normal
普通的
why are you so focused
你为何如此专注
Usually too busy
平时太忙
There is no time either.
也没有时间。
Relax and watch TV.
放松一下，看看电视。
so
所以
Although ugly,
虽然丑，
I think it's pretty
我觉得蛮漂亮的
Just a relaxing day
不过是轻松的一天
Almost over
快结束了
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
I have to go.
我得走了。
yes?
是？
Are you old?
你老了吗？
today?
今天？
still coming back?
还回来吗？
Probably won't come back
可能不会回来
Won't be back again.
不会再回来了。
Change the environment.
改变环境。
Not bad.
也不错。
will you miss me
你会想念我吗
want someone
想要一个人
It drove me into a dead end.
把我逼进了死胡同。
just got sick
刚刚生病了
You can only remember love for a longer time
只能更长久地记住爱情
so terrible.
太糟糕了。
I don't have this hobby.
我没有这个爱好。
before i go,
在我走之前，
Can I have a wish come true?
我可以实现一个愿望吗？
if i could do it
如果我能做到的话
Been eating my food for so long
吃了我的食物这么久了
No reply once
一次没回复
My cooking skills are terrible
我的厨艺太差了
I'm afraid you won't be able to eat
我怕你吃不下饭
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I can teach you.
我能教你。
OK
好的。
Remember, okay?
记住，好吗？
Some of these brands are pretty good
这些品牌有些还是不错的
Very, very happy
特别特别开心
Once you learn you already know
一旦你学习你就已经知道了
I'll teach you when I get home.
回家后我教你。
Don't always eat noodles right away.
不要总是立即吃面条。
It won't work immediately.
它不会立即起作用。
Cook curry rice
煮咖喱饭
Won't waste your time
不会浪费你的时间
enough.
足够的。
I rarely use it.
我很少用它。
After I left,
我离开后，
It feels like you're back
感觉就像你回来了
to the original life.
到原来的生活。
Have you set a departure time?
你定好出发时间了吗？
why are you interesting
你为什么有趣
Said such ugly words
说了这么难听的话
will gradually separate
会渐渐分开
This is also true.
这也是对的。
But when will I go?
但我什么时候去呢？
depends on when you
取决于你什么时候
mission accomplished.
完成任务。
I am
我是
What mission?
什么使命？
Go to biotech.
去生物公司。
retrieve data.
获取数据。
Did you find the wrong person?
你是不是找错人了？
I was with the National Security Agency.
我当时在国家安全局。
Not in biotech.
不在生物公司。
Tapi Huang Jiaming dan Huang Zicheng ada di sini.
Tapi Huang Jiaming dan Huang Zicheng ada di sini.
Why are you so...
为什么你这么...
let them participate
让他们参与
They can help you.
他们可以帮助你。
Didn't you expect me?
你没有期待我吗？
Go as soon as possible?
尽快去吗？
I can go
我可以去
certainly.
当然。
if you want to stop me
如果你想阻止我
I might as well consider staying here.
我也可以考虑留在这里。
after all,
毕竟，
I kind of like you.
我有点喜欢你。
like me?
像我这样的？
I'm no different
我没有什么不同
and your previous partner.
和你以前的伴侣。
They are just people you take advantage of.
他们只是你利用的人。
You are different from them.
你和他们不一样。
Is there any difference?
有什么不同吗？
You stand in the light.
你站在光里。
Create man
造人
have no idea.
不知道。
Now you have succeeded.
现在你已经成功了。
But recently I started to doubt
但最近我开始怀疑
Have you really come to darkness?
你真的来到黑暗了吗？
Every time I cook noodles for you
每次我给你煮面条
will you follow me
你会跟踪我吗
sometimes.
有时。
Code HY106.
代码 HY106。
Genetic engineering experiments.
基因工程实验。
The most important projects of biotech companies
生物公司最重要的项目
There is also Bajili.
还有八吉里。
the most important
最重要的
I can't immediately
我立刻就不能
such an important project
如此重要的项目
Even I don't know
就连我也不知道
what is that thing
那个东西是什么
There is no way out.
别无退路。
Yu Xiao Yue, Shi Lei, Xiang Yang.
Yu Xiao Yue, Shi Lei, Xiang Yang.
You caught them all.
都被你抓到了。
Huang Zicheng was also saved by you.
黄子成也是你救的。
everyone
每个人
Deleted by you
被你删除了
only you
只有你
If you can't,
如果你不能，
I can only go to your uncle
只能去找你叔叔了
The pot is over
锅已经结束了
try it.
尝试一下。
Since I'm so important
既然我如此重要
Let’s discuss the terms.
我们来讨论一下条款。
What conditions?
什么条件？
this is the last thing
这是最后一件事
For Bajiri.
为了八吉里。
Stop looking for me.
不要再找我了。
do you think you deserve it
你认为你值得
Discuss terms?
讨论条款？
Who are you
你是
You are just discussing terms.
你们只是在讨论条款。
Best qualifications.
最好的资格。
I will turn myself in to the National Security Bureau.
我会去国安局自首。
And take you once.
并带你一次。
You get nothing.
你什么也得不到。
Why do you two have to get hurt?
为什么你们两个一定要受伤？
Neither party was injured.
双方都没有受伤。
We were the only ones hurt.
我们是唯一受伤的人。
You have to see the situation clearly.
你必须看清楚情况。
What does Yagiri want now?
矢切现在想要什么
Experimental data only.
仅实验数据。
Both of us
我们俩
Just a game of chess.
只是一盘棋。
After all, I am more important than you.
毕竟我比你更重要。
To them,
对他们来说，
for them.
对于他们来说。
I don't know where it comes from
我不知道从哪里来
where does it come from
从哪里来
but i only know
但我只知道
They can kick you out at any time.
他们随时可以把你赶出去。
the only one who can do it
唯一能做到的人
who can help you
谁可以帮助你
it's me
是我
if you
如果你
Still can't see clearly
还是看不清情况
It will dig its own grave.
它会自掘坟墓。
Tell me all this.
告诉我这一切。
What do you want to tell me?
你想告诉我什么？
I'm just hoping you can convey this to me.
我只是希望你能帮我传达一下。
This is the final task
这是最后的任务
I did it for you.
我为你做的。
After that, I'll go with you.
在那之后，我会和你一起去。
Went together.
一起去了。
where to?
去哪儿？
foreign.
国外。
Why?
为什么？
I live here now.
我现在住在这里。
They still told me to work.
他们仍然告诉我要工作。
Sooner or later, the national security will catch you.
迟早会被国安抓到的。
I already
我已经
Can see the future.
可以看到未来。
Why didn't I escape earlier?
我为什么不早点逃走？
besides,
除此之外，
I also need rewards.
我还需要奖励。
How many?
多少？
1,000,000.
100万美元。
Feel this data
你感受一下这个数据
Worth 1 million?
值100万？
Not just data,
不仅仅是数据，
It's also your safety.
也是您的安全。
my safety
我的安全
Don't you think it's worth it?
你不觉得值得吗？
I can't make up my mind.
我拿不定主意。
I need to report to my superiors.
我要向上级汇报。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I'm waiting for your answer.
我在等待你的回答。
How does it feel?
感觉如何？
good.
不错。
He is very talented.
他非常有才华。
Go to the department head.
去部门长吧。
Your conditions are a bit extreme.
你的条件有点极端了。
You sacrificed many people,
你牺牲了很多人，
But got nothing.
但什么也没得到。
I can get it.
我能得到它。
Do you think my conditions are excessive?
你觉得我的条件过分吗？
But don't forget.
但不要忘记。
My biggest bargaining chip is not money,
我最大的筹码不是钱，
But your secret killed Xiao Yi.
但你的秘密害死了萧毅。
The secret is not a treasure chest.
这个秘密不是宝箱。
you let me
你让我
Work hard for you.
为你努力工作。
Every move is very dangerous.
每一个动作都是非常危险的。
If you continue like this
如果你继续这样下去的话
I won't succeed.
我不会成功。
There is only a dead end.
只有死路一条。
Might as well die early.
还不如早点死。
I give up now.
我现在就放弃了。
Maybe he won't be sentenced to death.
也许他不会被判处死刑。
Go to the department head.
去部门长吧。
your attitude...
你的态度...
we can't keep talking
我们不能继续说话
This is your task.
这是你的任务。
for me,
为我，
This is fate.
这就是命运。
OK
好的。
I promise you.
我答应你。
You bring something
你带东西来
Went with Zhang Taoke.
和张涛克一起去了。
Where is the money?
钱在哪里？
I will add it to your account.
我会将其添加到您的帐户中。
Thank you, Boss Yu.
谢谢余老板。
I don't know either
我也不知道
You can work for your boss or not.
可以为老板工作，也可以不为老板工作。
Depends on your performance.
取决于你的表现。
Do you really agree?
你真的同意吗？
syarat Gao Tianyang
syarat Gao Tianyang
have you ever thought about
你有没有想过
kenapa Gao Tianyang
kenapa Gao Tianyang
I want to go with Boss Zhang
想和张老板一起去
He doesn't want trouble...
他不想麻烦...
Huang Zicheng dan Huang Jiaming
Huang Zicheng dan Huang Jiaming
More worried about personal safety.
更担心人身安全。
perhaps
或许
Gao Tianyang thought for a long time
高天阳想了很久
Come to Night Caboose.
来到夜卡布斯。
I do not understand.
我不明白。
Try to think about it.
尝试思考一下。
Why not Gao Tianyang
为什么不是高天阳
membunuh Xiao Yi
membunuh Xiao Yi
He left himself a chance.
他给自己留下了机会。
Gao Tianyang meninggalkan Guo An
Gao Tianyang meninggalkan Guo An
useless
无用
For us.
为了我们。
Do you still agree to these terms?
您仍然同意这些条款吗？
Let's stabilize him first
我们先稳定他
But you can’t put all your chips in
但不能把所有的筹码都放进去
in his body.
在他身上。
I have another route.
我还有另一条路线。
How do you know I'm here?
你怎么知道我在这里？
You know, but you ask anyway.
你知道，但还是要问。
not everyone
不是每个人
Isn’t it all me?
不都是我吗？
This is also true.
这也是对的。
Why? Don't you want to see me?
为什么？你不想见我吗？
son.
儿子。
if you don't come to me
如果你不来找我
I still need to find you.
我还需要找到你。
Why are you looking for me?
你为什么找我？
Tell you
告诉你
My experience was lied to again
我的经验又被骗了
I was lied to.
我被骗了。
he gave me a way
他给了我一条路
Invitation into the trap
邀请进入陷阱
I'll go in honestly
我会诚实地进去
Do you still believe him?
你还相信他吗？
There is no way out.
别无退路。
Let people hold it until they die
让人们拿着它直到死去
like you,
喜欢你，
Do you still want to join Guoan?
还想进国安吗？
Although I was cheated this time
虽然这次我被骗了
But it was not Yaoyao who trapped me.
但困住我的并不是瑶瑶。
but you
但是你
Why me?
为什么我？
Yaoyao took the initiative
瑶瑶主动了
Who told me to investigate.
谁告诉我去调查的。
This is a trap.
这是一个陷阱。
i was arrested
我被捕了
It was planned before.
之前也计划过。
Why is he persecuting me?
他为什么要迫害我？
There is only one possibility
只有一种可能
he wants to use me
他想利用我
Change Zhu Zheri.
改变朱哲日。
kepada Joo Cheol-il。
kepada Joo Cheol-il。
They are all people of the Night Mist.
他们都是夜雾之人。
Why did he want to sacrifice me?
他为什么要牺牲我？
In order to gain Zhu Zheri's trust.
以取得朱哲日的信任。
Toward Zhu Zheri?
朝向朱哲日？
but...
但...
He works for others.
他为别人工作。
And this person
而这个人
maybe this is you
也许这就是你
correct?
正确的？
Go to the department head.
去部门长吧。
Today, you came to pick me up.
今天，你来接我了。
send me home
送我回家
the whole journey
整个旅程
you calmed my mood
你平静了我的情绪
You must tell me finally
最后一定要告诉我
In this way, Yao Ming and I
这样我和姚明
dengan Yao Yao
dengan Yao Yao
correct?
正确的？
of.
的。
Almost as you guessed
和你猜测的几乎一样
Your mission was accomplished well.
你的使命完成得很好
Who is angry?
谁生气了？
Have I completed the task?
我完成任务了吗
i had planned
我曾计划
if you want to hear what i have to say
如果你想听我说的话
Come out quietly.
静静地出来。
This thing won't
这东西不会
in your mind
在你的脑海里
Good, I know.
很好，我知道。
You won't soon
你马上就不会
Admit he was wrong.
承认他错了。
I do not care.
我不在乎。
Not just entered
不是刚进入的
Spent two days in the police station?
在派出所蹲了两天？
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
But there is one thing today
但今天有一件事
I have to ask you.
我得问你。
Is Yaoyao yours?
瑶瑶是你的人吗？
Does he work for you?
他为你工作吗？
of.
的。
no.
不是。
Brother, thank you, thank you
兄弟，谢谢你，谢谢你
thanks my brother
感谢我的兄弟
brother.
兄弟。
Are you crazy?
你疯了？
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
你为什么不早点告诉我？
when you
当你
keep in touch?
保持联系？
correct?
正确的？
when he begged you to save me
当他恳求你救我时
I've already explained
我已经解释过了
dengan Huang Zicheng.
dengan Huang Zicheng.
He won't look for me again.
他不会再找我了。
I have deleted his phone number.
我已经删除了他的电话号码。
this decision
这个决定
Good for both of you.
对你们俩都有好处。
I see.
我明白。
in my heart
在我心里
are you looking for me?
你在找我吗？
Are you serious?
你是认真的吗？
To calm my mind?
让我的心平静下来？
I want you to read a philosophy book.
我想让你看一本哲学书。
Why read philosophy books?
为什么要读哲学书？
I guess
我猜测
Related to agent games
与代理游戏相关
when you notice
当你注意到
You don't have to care.
你不必关心。
Who is in the philosophy book?
哲学书里有谁？
Can obtain data of 1 user
可以获取1个用户的数据
There is a data center.
有一个数据中心。
Customer information
客户资料
will be placed
将被放置
in the server.
在服务器中。
Data is accessible to many people.
很多人都可以接触到数据。
But it can be transferred.
但可以转让。
Not many people have personal information.
拥有个人信息的人并不多。
I'll pay attention.
我会注意的。
You need to pay attention.
你需要注意。
Zhu Zheyi.
朱哲一.
OK
好的。
I know I know.
我知道我知道。
Must be kept confidential.
必须保密。
if you don't want to tell me
如果你不想告诉我
It doesn't matter
没关系
As long as Yaoyao can go ashore,
只要瑶瑶能上岸，
I can do anything.
我什么事都能做。
If I don't let you meet
如果我不让你见面
can you do it
你可以做到吗
I can.
我可以。
As long as I can save him
只要我能救他
I will never see him again.
我再也见不到他了。
Can you let it go?
你能放开它吗？
cannot.
不能。
But you have to let go.
但必须放手。
You can continue to see him.
你可以继续见他。
that's right.
这是正确的。
You tried to steal.
你试图偷窃。
and was arrested and taken to the police station.
并被逮捕到警察局。
He is the one who asked Zhu Zhe to let you go.
他就是那个要求朱哲放你走的人。
You two still have feelings for each other.
你们俩还是有感情的。
Go out, don't go find him
你出去吧，你不去找他
Illogical.
不合逻辑。
I got you.
我明白你的意思。
but,
但，
I think
我觉得
It's not easy.
这并不容易。
Before the case ends,
在案件结束之前，
Anything can happen.
任何事情都可能发生。
Keep your feelings.
保持你的感觉。
I know.
我知道。
Don't worry, brother.
兄弟，别担心。
I will not let you down.
我不会让你失望。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I took a step back.
我退后一步。
A public prosecution was launched against Huang Zicheng.
对黄子成提起公诉。
It's a misunderstanding.
是一个误会。
He should thank you.
他应该感谢你。
Guess what he is thinking now.
你猜他现在在想什么。
have no idea.
不知道。
But I think this decision
但我认为这个决定
It must be good for him.
一定对他有好处。
Stay away from the fight.
远离战斗。
Aren't you afraid that he will doubt you?
你就不怕他怀疑你吗？
why are you worried
你为什么担心
all of these
所有这些
According to his plan.
按照他的计划。
He himself is very careless
他自己也很不小心
Reveal yourself.
显露自己。
Why do you doubt me?
你为什么怀疑我？
Do you really think so?
你真的这样想吗？
He trusts you very much.
他非常信任你。
In this world,
在这世上，
who can
谁可以
Trust others?
信任别人？
that's right
这是正确的
since you came in
自从你进来
to the world of espionage,
到间谍世界，
you should have
你应该有
this mental list
这个心理清单
suspect each other, deceive each other
互相猜疑，互相欺骗
It will always be with you.
它会一直陪伴着你。
But I'm not like you.
但我不像你。
I'm not as strong as you.
我没有你那么坚强。
I know
我知道
Almost there
就快到了
own limit.
自己的极限。
I have no other choice.
我没有别的办法。
continue again
再次继续
I'm like now
我现在就像
who is struggling
谁在挣扎
Fish in the lake.
湖里的鱼。
Take a deep breath.
深吸一口气。
panting
气喘吁吁
【Waiting to die at any time. 】
【随时等死。】
If you can leave Jinhai,
如果你能离开金海，
what are you going to do?
你会怎样做？
stay away from fighting
远离战斗
find a job
找工作
Like to read philosophy
喜欢读哲学
If the agent's mission
如果代理人的使命
Can be of the same type
可以是同一类型
simple game
简单的游戏
I do not need
我不需要
every day.
每天。
You are a great player.
你是一位出色的球员。
Night fog won't be that easy.
夜雾不会那么容易。
I'll let you go.
我会让你离开。
so,
所以，
I don't have a choice.
我没有选择的权利。
I can't make up my mind
我拿不定主意
I can't make up my mind myself.
我自己拿不定主意。
Wait a moment.
等一下。
Maybe I can help you.
我或许可以帮助你。
how is it like?
什么样的？
Please leave Jinhai.
请离开金海。
Really?
真的吗？
I can recommend you
我可以推荐你
To Mr. Z
致Z先生
Let you enter the game company
让你进入游戏公司
and become a game director
并成为一名游戏监督
New mission design
新的任务设计
to develop new players.
来培养新球员。
would you like
你是否愿意
I do.
我愿意。
I am very willing to
我非常愿意
Thank you, Principal Zhou
谢谢周校长
but there is a condition
但有一个条件
speak out.
说出来。
What are my conditions?
我的条件是什么？
Any conditions.
任何条件。
you said.
你说的。
If you leave,
如果你走的话，
This means our game
这意味着我们的游戏
lost a great player
失去了一位伟大的球员
you need to find someone else
你需要找别人
bring him back
带他回来
to take your place.
来取代你的职位。
Find someone else.
找别人。
that's right
这是正确的
Who are you looking for?
你在找谁？
Huang Zicheng.
Huang Zicheng.
Why did you bring him here?
你为什么带他来？
Isn't this
这不是吗
What is your mission in Gimhae?
你来金海的使命是什么？
Bring him back.
带他回来。
Your mission will be accomplished.
你的使命将会完成。
you can start
你可以开始了
your new life.
你的新生活。
But now he...
但现在他...
useless
无用
no longer useful
不再有用
Dan Gao Tianyang
Dan Gao Tianyang
This is the situation of Mr. Yu
这是于先生的情况
I can only help so much
我只能帮助这么多
No heart?
没有心吗？
no
不是
Then there is nothing
然后就什么都没有了
Very hesitant.
很犹豫。
You said before that you had no choice
之前你说过你别无选择
now i give you
现在，我给你
There is a chance to choose.
有机会选择。
think carefully.
仔细想想。